emarsys.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Emarsys

## Emarsys Privacy Policy

### Information Tracking and Usage

To the extent it is permitted by applicable laws, Emarsys eMarketing Systems AG (in the following referred to as “Emarsys” or “we”) tracks and gathers certain information on this website that helps us to better understand our visitors’ needs related to our website and our services. We will never share this information with third parties unless explicitly stated upon subscription, in this policy or ordered by a court of law. When data sharing will occur, the third party or parties will be referenced explicitly at the point of subscription. If you have signed up for email marketing, the personal data that you gave upon registration will be used to send you personalized newsletters, product news, valuable tips and exclusive offers. Subscribers can withdraw their consent to receive marketing communications by using the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each email, or by emailing [unsubscribe@emarsys.com](mailto:unsubscribe@emarsys.com).

### Request of Information

On some pages of our website users have the option to register for various Emarsys services – e.g. newsletter, download of whitepapers, etc. – using data capture forms. These forms usually require the user’s name, email address, company, as well as other information that is necessary to provide the requested service. The user may choose to provide additional non-mandatory information that enables us to provide a more personalized service. To the extent it is permitted by applicable laws, we may also directly contact website users based on the information they have provided to promote Emarsys’ products. In case of requests from countries in which Emarsys does not handle requests itself but they are handled by affiliated companies or other representatives, we may also transfer the data to the responsible affiliated company or representative for said purpose (in each case only to the extent it is permitted by applicable laws). The users can object to the use of their data as described above at any time by emailing [dataprotection@emarsys.com.](mailto:dataprotection@emarsys.com)

### Cookies

Our website uses “cookies”. Cookies help us understand our visitors’ needs and interests, and we use that information to improve our website and the services offered on the individual pages. They are not linked to any personally identifiable information. If a user rejects the cookie, our site may still be used, however the user’s access to some areas of our website may be limited.

A “cookie” is a small text file containing a random and unique identifier that either Emarsys or a business partner, such as a third-party web analytics provider, transfers to your computer through your web browser (unless you set your browser to reject cookies). Emarsys uses cookies to, among other things, recognize your browser, track your movement through the website, to track the point of registration for those users signing up for mailings or programs, and to track and measure the success of a marketing campaign.

Emarsys specifically uses Google Analytics and re-targeting cookies to allow 3rd party service providers to provide advertisements on our behalf across the internet. These service providers may collect your IP address and non-personal data about your visits. This is completely anonymous and does not include your name, address, email address or other personal information. Additionally, these cookies are used to gather anonymous statistical information on how the website is browsed. These cookies will expire after 10 years.

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. For more information about cookies, including how to set your internet browser to reject cookies, please go to [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). You can specifically opt-out of Google Analytics using [this tool](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### Shared Usage of Data

We reserve the right to share accumulated, general demographic data for statistical purposes with selected partners. These data do not contain any personally identifiable information.

### Contacts Under Sixteen Years of Age

Emarsys does not specifically target anyone under the age of sixteen. Persons under the age of sixteen are not permitted to use the Emarsys marketing platform.

### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please note that Emarsys is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other websites to which we link.

### Other Types of Information Gathering

Occasionally our website gathers visitors’ data via temporary marketing activities such as webinars, free trial accounts, surveys, etc. Participation in these activities is on a voluntary basis, which allows the visitor to decide whether to disclose any personal data or not. Such data may include, but is not limited to, contact information (e.g. name, email, phone number) and demographic information (e.g. zip code, date of birth). The data will be used to provide the visitor with the service requested. Data gathered via surveys will be used for improving our website and services. Where explicit consent is given, data provided will also be used for Emarsys marketing communications, such as email and direct mail. The subscription details can be referenced on the form being filled. Further information can be found under the sub-header ‘Information Tracking and Usage’ within this policy.

### Changing/Editing Personal Information

Users can change, edit or remove any information provided to us at the time of registration for an Emarsys service by resubmitting details via an online form, or by completing a contact request on the website. In the instance that a user seeks solely to remove personal information, the request can be made by emailing [dataprotection@emarsys.com](mailto:dataprotection@emarsys.com).

### Email Marketing

By subscribing to our email marketing, you will be the first to learn about new products, valuable tips and news as well as exclusive offers. After signing up you will receive a confirmation email with an activation link to start receiving the newsletter. Emails will be sent from or include the brand name ‘Emarsys’ within. Email sending frequency will vary. If you no longer wish to receive our emails you can unsubscribe at any time, simply by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the footer of any of our emails. Alternatively, consent can be withdrawn by emailing _[unsubscribe@emarsys.com](mailto:unsubscribe@emarsys.com)_.

We use the email address specified during a purchase (including email addresses provided to Emarsys for using the purchased Emarsys services) for direct marketing activities for our own similar products or services. These mailings are intended to inform you about the product(s) you have bought. You are able to unsubscribe without costs other than the transmission costs pursuant to the basic rates being incurred in this regard by clicking on the link in every email or by sending us an email to _[unsubscribe@emarsys.com](mailto:unsubscribe@emarsys.com)_.

In addition to direct marketing, we might use the email addresses, which you have provided to Emarsys, for sending you marketing based on one or more of the following legal bases: (i) your consent (Art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR), (ii) necessity for the performance of our contracted services to you (Art. 6 (1) lit. b GDPR), and (iii) our legitimate interests (Art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR).

### Unsubscribe

Users who wish to no longer receive promotional emails may click on a link named “unsubscribe” which is embedded in every email sent by Emarsys. Alternatively, consent can be withdrawn by emailing _[unsubscribe@emarsys.com](mailto:unsubscribe@emarsys.com)_.

### Referral Service

If a visitor decides to use our referral service in order to inform a friend or colleague about our website, we request the name and email address of the recipient. Following this, Emarsys sends exactly one automated message to the friend or colleague, with an invitation to visit our website. Emarsys does not store the corresponding data.

### External Service Providers

For certain activities related to this website we have retained the services of external data processors (e.g. data centers). These service providers process data only in accordance with our instructions, are therefore also bound by this privacy policy, and are subject to our control. Under no circumstances may these service providers use any data that are collected and processed in relation to this website for their own purposes.

### Notification in Case of Policy Change

Should we decide to change our privacy policy, we will notify users of such changes on our website. This keeps our users up to date about which information we gather, how we use this information, whether that information is disclosed to third parties, and if yes, in which way.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

Emarsys North America Inc  
10 W Market St., Suite 1350  
Indianapolis, IN 46204

 **Phone** : +1 844-693-6277  
**Fax** : +1 317-663-1117  
**Email** : [us@emarsys.com](mailto:us@emarsys.com)  
**Web** :[ www.emarsys.com](http://www.emarsys.com/)

### Data protection officer:

 **Szabolcs Steiner**  
+43147820800  
Emarsys eMarketing Systems AG  
Märzstrasse 1  
1150 Vienna  
Austria
